我们还需要买红酒 芝士 鲜花...
Okay, we still need wine, cheese, flowers --
我们还得去一趟蛋糕房
Oh, we have to stop by the bakery.
是 我们还得买个礼物献给女主人
Yeah, and we need a hostess gift
毕竟这是朗吉尼斯办的"感朋节派对"
for Longinus' Friendsgiving party.
客人空手上门 他可不会给什么好脸色
You know, she does not look kindly on an empty-handed guest.
-太过了 -我懂的
- It's too much. - I know.
但你对这种人能有多高指望呢
But what do you expect from somebody
毕竟他把名字
who changed their name
都从拉里·琼斯改成朗吉尼斯·圣杰梅茵了
from Larry Jones to Longinus St. Germaine?
不是 我是说这清单上的东西过多
No, I mean this list.
听着 我们要想4点赶到我爸家
Okay, we're only making it to my dad's by 4:00
只能不去参加曾用名为拉里的人举办的派对了
if we blow off the hostess formerly known as Larry.
不要 他的派对是我对于感恩节最爱的部分
No! His party's my favorite thing about Thanksgiving!
桌上的人轮流发表感言
Like, when we all go around the table
感恩一件今年没让人烦心的好事
and say one thing we're thankful for not wearing this year.
不 不行 抱歉
No. No, I'm sorry. Sorry.
就算不参加派对 恐怕最多也只够踩着点到
Even skipping the party, we're barely gonna make it in time.
好了 给
Alright. Here.
我们分配一下 弄完在这里会合
Let's divvy these up and meet back here.
好吧 行
Okay, fine.
-你好啊 米奇 -你好 罗纳多
- Oh, hi, Mitch! - Hi, Ronaldo.
让我猜猜 这是给朗吉尼斯买的吗
What -- Let me guess. Those are for Longinus?
我可不会给那个毒舌女王买这种烂东西
I would never get something this shabby for that judgy queen.
-不是 我妈在住院 -天啊
- No, my mom is in the hospital. - Oh, my God.
你们会去参加派对吗
Will I see you guys at the party?
恐怕不行
Oh, unfortunately no.
今天已经变成一个噩梦了
Uh, this day has turned into something of a nightmare.
小卡去哪儿了
Where's Cam?
我们刚刚分开了
We just split up.
我们需要太多不同的东西
We just needed so many different things,
还是分开比较好
it was easier to separate.
总之 感恩节快乐
So, anyway, happy Thanksgiving.
代我向大家问好
Tell everyone I said hi.
比悲伤更悲伤的故事
Super sad news.
猜猜谁刚刚分手了
Guess who just broke up.
给个提示 你欠我50块
Hint -- you owe me 50 bucks.
卢克 别再吃棉花糖了
Luke, stop eating all the marshmallows.
这些红薯需要一切能帮忙的人手来处理
Those yams need all the help that they can get.
艾丽克斯 馅料怎么样了
Alex, how's the stuffing?
你说呢
You tell me.
我们为什么要过这个傻兮兮的节日
Why do we even have this stupid holiday?
我爸和我妈对我们太好了
Mom and Dad have been incredible --
让我 迪兰和双胞胎跟他们一起生活
letting me, Dylan, and the twins live with them,
帮忙在夜间喂奶 给他们讲睡前故事
helping with midnight feedings, bedtime stories.
迪兰超爱我爸随角色变声讲故事
Dylan loves it when my dad does the voices.
所以 我想给我妈放个假
So, I'm giving my mom a break
今年就不用她来准备感恩节晚餐了
from cooking Thanksgiving dinner.
我想做点特别的事
I wanted to do something special
感谢他们在我身边支持我
to thank them for being there for me.
对不起 我只是...
I'm sorry. I've just, um...
我变成了好美好的一个人啊
I've become such a beautiful person.
感恩节快乐 杰
Happy Thanksgiving, Jay.
如果你想跟我一起看 我可以往这边挪点
Oh, I can slide over if you want to watch this with me.
不 我从来都不懂没有坦克的游行有什么意义
Nah. I never saw the point of a parade without tanks.
我想带这个飞机出去兜兜风
I'm gonna take the plane out for a spin.
你想一起去吗
You want to come with?
我吗
Me?
去 飞行吗
Go...fly?
我装得很淡定 但我内心是狂喜的
I played it cool, but I was pretty jazzed.
距离上次杰叫我出去
It's been 10 years since Jay asked me
跟他一起玩航模飞机已经有十年了 我...
to go model-plane flying with him, and I was, uh...
我非常迫切地希望能用更美好的记忆
I was eager to replace that memory
来替换掉上次的不堪
with a -- a be-- a better one.
好了 开始吧
Okay, let's do it!
你们去哪儿啊
Where are you guys going?
没什么特别的
Oh, nowhere special.
就是杰邀我加入他的高空俱乐部[飞机上做爱]
Let's just say that Jay's asked me to join his mile high club.
别说这种让人误会的话
Let's not say that.
好酷
Cool!
多年前 我差点就加入了
You know, years ago, I almost joined
女性主导的空姐世界
the female-dominated world of flight attendants.
我的护士同伴们现在还拿这事刺激我呢
My fellow nurses still needle me about it.
我能一起去吗
Can I come?
实际上 杰对于...
Uh, actually, Jay's pretty particular about --
行吧 有何不可
Sure, why not?
看来我们要玩三人行了哦
Looks like we're having a threesome!
你这是在自取其辱
You're embarrassing yourself.
火鸡的中间部分还是冰冻的
The turkey is still frozen in the middle!
外热 内冷
Hot on the outside, cold on the inside --
真是让我想起了某个人呢
reminds me of a certain someone.
-求你别问是谁 -好的
- Please don't ask. - Sure.
这个馅料太酸了
Ugh, this pie filling is so sour.
是啊 当你指望某样东西如蜜一样甜
Yeah, it's devastating when you expect something to be sweet
结果沦落成性心理的强烈折磨 真让人伤心欲绝
but ends up being intense psychosexual torture.
我不想谈论这事
I don't want to talk about it.
-那可太好了 -别担心
- Cool, cool. - Don't worry.
卢克著名的果冻杂烩将拯救你们
Luke's famous Jell-o mold is here to save your sorry butts.
我这么多年来就为爸妈做这么一件事
I can't have the one nice thing I've done
我不能让它成为灾难
for Mom and Dad be a disaster!
艾丽克斯 能请你联系在跟你交往的那个大厨吗
Alex, um, call you please call that chef that you're dating?
那个自大的怪胎吗
That pompous weirdo?
我故意赶在节前跟他分手了啊
I purposely broke up with him before the holidays.
如果我现在打给他
If I call him now,
就不得不跟他凑合到新年前了
I will be stuck with him until New Year's.
有一种思想流派认为
There's a school of thought
可能要咬牙坚持到情人节
it can even stretch out to Valentine's Day.
一旦过了感恩节 那后面就是狂野大西部了
Once you pass Thanksgiving, it's the Wild West.
好吧我说 她叫杰西卡
Okay! Her name is Jessica.
我们是在圣塔安娜强风盛行时认识的
We met during a Santa Ana wind,
我们都知道雷蒙德·钱德勒的名言...
and we all know what Raymond Chandler said --
那就没必要重复了
So no need to repeat it.
艾丽克斯 拜托了 你那个大厨能有多怪
Alex, please. How weird can your chef be?
我不知道是不是因为他是个大厨
I don't know if it's 'cause he's a chef
大厨的控制欲都比较强
and they can be controlling,
我知道爱的语言有很多种不同的表达方式
and I know there's lots of different "love languages,"
但是 ...
but...
他把我当木偶一样操控
he puppets me.
一定要超级薄和均匀才行 就像这样
You want them to be super thin and uniform, like this.
洋葱把你熏得流眼泪了
You're tearing up from the onions.
擤一下
And blow.
我还是去洗手间处理一下吧
You know, maybe I'll just go to the bathroom and do this.
好的 我们走
Okay. Sure. Let's go.
乔 你在准备座次卡吗
Oh, Joe! You're doing place cards?
一般不都是曼尼来做这事吗
Doesn't Manny usually take care of seating?
他"在经历一些事"
He's "going through something."
我相信他很快就会忍不住全都说出来的
I'm sure we'll hear a spoken word about it soon enough.
你真的快要变成我爸的4英尺小版了
You really are turning into a 4-foot version of my dad.
是我们的爸爸
Our dad.
那还真是"永远都不会怪"呢
That will never not be weird.
歌洛莉亚 你竟然洗衣服
Gloria, you do laundry?
还是说你在遮孕肚
Or are you hiding a pregnancy?
不是 女佣辞职了
No. The housekeeper quit.
我真的很爱全职为菲尔工作 虽然薪资很少
I really love working for Phil full-time for very little money,
但我当时没意识到
but I didn't realize
要平衡家庭和工作有多难
how hard it was going to be balancing everything.
我懂 所以我才爱不工作的感觉
I know. That's why I love not working.
终于有时间把各种事都做掉了
Finally, enough time to get everything done.
当真吗
Really?
你不怀念面对各种新挑战的感觉吗
You don't miss facing new challenges,
以及竞争的刺激
the fire of competition,
和那种成就感
that sense of accomplishment?
不 一点都不
No. No.
当然了 我曾担心过我是那种
I mean, of course, I worried I was the type of person
需要一直忙碌才心安的人 但那就像是毒品
who needed to be busy all the time, but it's like a drug --
经过几周的戒断
after a couple of weeks of withdrawal,
我终于适应什么也不干的生活了
I am finally comfortable doing nothing.
你买的是什么样的馅饼
Oh, what kind of pie did you get,
南瓜瓜馅 山核桃桃馅 还是甜土豆豆馅的
pun'kin, pee-can, sweet pataytuh?
无面粉巧克力蛋糕
Flourless chocolate cake.
你试试把这说出一股乡村味儿来
Let's see you try and country that up.
我的手机在口袋里
My phone's in my pocket.
你能帮我拿一下吗 我够不着
Here, would you grab it? I can't get it.
好了
Alright.
-是谁 -乔撒姆发来短信
- Who is it? - Oh, it's from Jotham.
"我刚听说了 非常遗憾 你还好吗"
"Just heard. I'm so sorry. How are you doing?"
-他在说什么 -我不知道
- What's that about? - I have no idea.
是勒迈克
Oh, L'Michael.
-"我的心与你同在 卡麦小芝士 打给我" -啥
- "Sending all my love, Camembert. Call me." - What?
阿耳特弥斯
Artemis.
"罗纳多告诉我你和米奇尔的事了
"Ronaldo told me about you and Mitchell.
心碎表情 眼泪表情
Broken-heart emoji, tear emoji,
老牌喜剧女星塔米·菲·贝克痛哭表情包"
Tammy Faye Bakker crying Gif."
罗纳多到底跟他说了什么啊
What did Ronaldo tell him?
不知道啊 我刚在这碰见他 他问你在哪
No clue. I-I just saw him here, and he asked where you were,
我就说我们分开去购物...
and I told him that we split up to shop and that --
我的天 他以为我们真的分手了
Oh, my God. He thinks we actually split up.
结果这消息就传遍基圈了
Oh, and it's gone viral.
有两样东西是基佬不肯坐[藏不住]的
Well, there are two things a gay can't sit on --
直男坐的丑塑料休闲椅和猛料大八卦
a plastic patio chair and a juicy bit of gossip.
不过看到我们的朋友这么有爱 也很感动啦
Well, it's nice to see how supportive our friends are being.
是啊 他们真好 第一时间就联系...
Yeah. It's nice how quickly they reached out to --
你一个人
to you.
我什么都没收到
I got nothing.
这铃声简直就是在嘲笑我
It's like it's mocking me.
这些短信肯定是发给我们两个看的啦
I-I'm sure the texts were meant for both of us.
才不是这样的 好吗
That's not how it works, okay?
他们又不是在感谢我们招待的早午餐
They're not thanking us for brunch.
我们可是要离婚了
We're getting a divorce!
为什么没人打给我啊
Why is no one calling me?!
或许因为他们认为你比起我...
Well, maybe because they think you're the --
更坚强 没那么感情用事
the stronger, less emotional one.
真是疯了 我坚强
That's crazy. Just because I'm strong
也不代表我在这种时候就不需要朋友们的关怀啊
doesn't mean I don't need my friends at a time like this!
什么时候
A time like what?
你知道我们不是真的要离婚的吧
Y-You realizing this isn't actually happening, right?
少来
Oh, come on.
如果情况反过来 你肯定会慌得一批
If the shoe was on the other foot, you would be freaking out.
没错 所以现在我才会收到这些短信啊
Yes -- which is why I'm getting all the texts.
好吧 你看
Okay, well, here.
是身在意大利卡普里岛的斯蒂芬和斯蒂凡
Ohh, from Steven and Stefan in Capri.
回短信跟他们说 "别特地飞回来 我没事"
Oh. Text back, uh, "Do not fly home. I'm doing okay."
我们难道不是没要离婚吗
I thought this wasn't really happening!
桶滚后接个S形转弯
Barrel roll into an S-turn...
再来一招我自创的"普里契特急转"
and a little thing I call Pritchett-Switch-It.
看起来就是普通的右转啊
That just looks like a right-hand turn.
你这外行当然看不懂门道啦
It would to an amateur.
你简直是艺术家 杰
You're an artist, Jay.
天空就是你的画布
The sky's your canvas.
要不要来玩"穿针引线"
Oh, should we do the hoop?
好主意
Great idea.
冠军 拿着这个走到空地中间
Hey, champ, take this out to the middle of the field
然后高举过头
and hold it up.
太棒了
Awesome!
这次轮到"冠军"是吧
Guess it's "champ's" turn.
真的不用让冠军先看看
Are -- Are we sure champ doesn't need to see
正确玩法是怎样吗
how it's done properly first?
不只是傻站在那就行了
I mean, it's not just standing there.
迪兰 站在那就行
Dylan, just stand there!
好棒
Yes!
这共同经历也太美好了
What a wonderful shared experience!
继续站在那
Now, stay out there.
我们再玩一次
We'll do it again.
这小子有天分 一点都没退缩
Kid's a natural. He didn't even flinch.
到底是勇敢还是纯粹迟钝 我们不会知道了
Bravery or a sluggish brain -- guess we'll never know.
抱歉
Sorry.
我就是有点不爽
Just, uh, I'm -- I'm a little annoyed
迪兰强行加入专属于我们的游戏
that Dylan's horning in on our thing.
其实我手指有点抽筋了
Hey, you know what, my hands are cramping up.
你想接手玩一下吗
You want to take over for me here?
-真的吗 -嗯
- Really? - Yeah.
谢谢
Thanks.
听着 你生迪兰的气 有没有可能
Listen, i-is it possible that you're angry at Dylan
不只是因为今天的事
for something more than today?
今早他的确吃掉了最后一块华夫饼
Well, he did take the last waffle this morning.
我觉得是因为... 他抢走了你第一个孩子
I think it's more about -- he took your firstborn.
我也经历过
Now, I've been there.
有这种想法很正常
It's only natural, you know.
我们当爸爸的 对女儿的保护欲很强 但是...
Us dads, we're very protective of our daughters, but, uh...
事实上 你可能会很有冲动
In fact, you may get a very strong impulse
把飞机直接撞向那家伙
to fly that plane right into the guy,
但别那么做
but don't do it.
什么 我绝不会伤害迪兰的
What? I-I would -- I would never hurt Dylan.
你怎么会觉得我会有那种冲动
Why would you even think I'd have that impulse?
我不知道 我就是觉得...
I don't know. I thought...
你刚才看他的眼神...
you know, the way you were looking at him....
等等
Wait.
你十年前就是那么想的吗
Is that what you were thinking 10 years ago?
这么多年来 我一直以为是我出错了
A-All this time, I thought it was my fault!
我在最后一刻脑袋动了
I-I moved my head at the last second.
其实你是故意撞到我的
But you hit me on purpose!
别说傻话 我只是...
Don't be ridiculous! I just --
只是什么 杰
You just what, Jay?
觉得用飞机撞上我的脸会很好玩是吗
Thought it'd be fun to fly a plane into my face?
什么样的冷血怪物才能对另一个人类做出这种...
What kind of monster does that to another human be--
糟了
Aw, no.
看都伤什么样了
Look at this.
这样应该就可以了
Okay, I think it's good for now.
没错 你需要享受你的私人时间
Oh, yeah, yeah. You need to enjoy your "me" time.
没错
Yeah.
昨天 我有三栋房子办了开放参观
Yesterday, I had three open houses.
我从早到晚都忙个不停
I was running around all day,
解决各种问题 创造各种价值
solving problems, creating value...
真是累死我了
Ay, it was exhausting.
我可不怀念这种感觉
Yeah. Don't miss that.
其中一栋房子可脏了
Oh, and one of the houses was filthy!
所有窗户都该清洗了
All the windows needed to be washed.
不过我也没脸说人家啦
But I am one to talk.
照我说的去做 我们就能拯救这顿饭
Follow my instructions, and we can save this meal.
-你哪位 -曼尼
- Who are you? - Manny.
错 在这个厨房里 你没有名字 搅拌
Wrong. In this kitchen, you don't have a name. Stir.
你这态度挺有意思的
Well, this is a fun energy.
你不会正好有个表妹
Do you happen to have a cousin
特别喜欢穿短裙 又喜怒无常吧
partial to Western skirts and terrifying mood swings?
我们需要他 闭嘴乖乖干活
We need him. Just do it.
这些胡萝卜切得一塌糊涂
Those carrots are a mess.
应该这样切
It's like this.
等等 什么
Wait, what --
老天
Oh, man.
你真的很知道自己想要什么
You really know what you want.
我觉得好有安全感
I feel so safe.
那个要再加点盐
That needs more salt.
那个要再加点奶油
That needs more cream.
艾丽克斯 那烤箱里有个蛋奶酥
And, Alex, I have a souffle in that oven
正英勇地膨胀升起
valiantly trying to rise.
你能不能别死命用力砸核桃
Would you mind not pounding those walnuts
你以为你是《巴黎圣母院》里猛敲钟的钟楼怪人吗
like you're Quasimodo just going at his bell?
知道吗 尼尔 我不知道如何...
You know what, Neil? I don't know how --
这个会不会太热啦
Are these too hot?
克莱尔 你为什么在清洗我们家的窗户
Claire? Why are you washing our windows?
我不知道
I don't know.
它们很脏 你妈又找到了一根长杆
They were really dirty, and your mom found a pole.
说来也巧
You know, funny coincidence --
上周 有人请我去一家制造杆子的公司
last week, I was offered the top job
任职高层
at a company that makes poles.
对 我也正在经历人生难关
Yeah, I'm going through something, too.
总之 我拒绝了那份工作
Anyway, I turned the job down,
但现在我又重新开始考虑去不去
but I think I'm reconsidering it.
她叫杰西卡
Her name is Jessica.
我知道杆子不像衣柜那么性感迷人
I know that poles aren't as sexy as closets.
但人们好像真的很喜欢杆子
But people really seem to like them,
而且它们出了名地不受经济衰退影响
and they are famously recession-proof.
天啊 我想我犯了个严重的错误
Oh, God. I think I made a terrible mistake.
我得打给那些人 接受那份工作 不然就给别人了
I got to call those people and get that job before it goes away.
-因为 -别打 克莱尔 那工作配不上你
- Because -- - Don't do it, Claire! It's beneath you!
曼尼 放尊重点
Manny, show some respect!
要是没有杆子
If it weren't for poles,
你向国旗宣誓就会像对脚踏垫宣誓了
you would be pledging allegiance to a floor mat!
-把手机给我 -不给
- Now, give me my phone! - No!
你不能在过渡期轻易接受备胎
You can't take a job on the rebound.
那只能让你开心一下
It'll feel good for a minute,
可之后你会坠入多疑与悔恨的虚空
but then you're plummeting down a K-hole of paranoia and regret.
你这周过得如何
How was your week?
好吧 我告诉你我为什么穿了高领衫
Fine. I'll tell you why I'm wearing a turtleneck.
在雪莉甩了我后
After Sherry dumped me,
我和第一个看得上我的女孩交往了
I dated the first girl who would have me --
讽刺的是 她是校篮球队的篮板王[备胎]
ironically, the leading rebounder on our basketball team.
这是被她用护齿牙套打的
That's where she hit me with her mouth guard.
我试过和她分手
I've tried to leave her,
可她单手抓住我的头 让我只能原地跑
but she just palms my head, and I run in place.
很遗憾你经历了这些 曼尼
Well, I'm sorry this is happening to you, Manny,
但这和我有什么...
but what does this have to do with --
她就是杆子公司 克莱尔
She's the pole company, Claire.
从我的错误中学习经验
Learn from my mistake --
除非你想被拍下
unless you want a compromising Polaroid of you
你被挂在女生更衣室高处的耻辱照
hung up very high in the women's locker room.
这梯子一会借我用用吧
I might need to borrow that ladder later.
克莱尔
Claire!
你稍后想不想帮我在购物网站
Do you want to help me shop online later
选一些职业装
for some power suits?
老天 我真怀念能像你这样
Oh, God, I miss wearing comfortable clothes
一直穿着舒适的衣服
all the time, like you do.
是啊 听起来很有趣
Yep. It sounds like a lot of fun.
我
I --
我在做什么
What am I doing?
做得好极了 再接再厉
A terrific job. Keep going!
不
N-no!
我自打到这以后就一直在冒汗
I have been sweating ever since I got here.
你是不是骗我帮你做家务
Did you trick me into doing your housework?
没有
No.
你手机根本没响
That phone did not ring!
你走开是因为你知道你有罪
You're walking away because you know you're guilty!
把鞋脱了 我刚擦过地
And take those shoes off! I just did the floors!
朋友们对我们"离婚"的反应
My friends' reaction to our "divorce"
真的让我很不舒服
really bothered me.
于是我对小卡找了个借口
So I made an excuse to Cam
然后去了朗吉尼斯的派对
and went over to Longinus' party.
我想让朋友们知道
I wanted the friends to know
我和小卡一样在情感上总要人哄
that I am just as emotionally needy as Cam!
妹子
Hey, girl, hey!
真不敢相信你来了
I can't believe you came.
我的天 小卡还好吗
Oh, my God. How's Cam?!
-是啊 他还好吗 -小卡很好 他没事
- Yes, how is he? - Cam's fine. He's fine.
那不过是个大误会
It was just a big misunderstanding.
我们没有离婚
We're not getting a divorce.
妹子 快进来
Well, girl, come on in.
让我给你拿两杯酒
Let's get you two drinks --
毕竟你两手空空来了派对 一手一杯
one for each empty hand you showed up to the party with.
我真的需要喝一杯
Well, I-I could use it.
尽管我们没有真的离婚
I mean, even though it's-it's not true about the divorce,
说不定某天就真的离了
it could be -- you know, someday.
这让我 让我特别...
And that just-that just makes me so, so...
困惑
Confused?
生气 愤怒
Angry? Furious.
《速度与激情》
"The Fast and the Furious"!
这不是在玩猜谜游戏
Okay, this isn't charades.
我很悲伤
I'm sad.
-那是你悲伤的表情吗 -是的
- That's your sad? - Yes.
-那是你悲伤的表情 -是的
- That's your sad? - Yeah.
我现在真的很需要你们的支持
And I-I really need your support right now.
等等 他有点新状况
Wait, something new is happening.
我的天
Oh, my God!
你们怎么看不出我现在有多真情流露
How can you not see how emotionally raw I am right now?
世事无常
Nothing lasts forever.
一切结束后我们该何去何从
What happens when it's over?
可怜的小卡 他是那么脆弱
Poor Cam. He is so fragile.
-他肯定会发疯 -我们会陪他熬过去的
- He's really gonna lose it. - We'll be there for him.
有谁会帮我拭去这些泪水
Who will be there to dry these tears?
哪有泪水
What tears?
泪水在哪呢
Where they at?
不 又来了
Ay, no, not again!
这次不是我 是他自己撞的
It wasn't me this time. He did it to himself.
和上次不一样
Unlike last time,
上次是你故意让飞机撞到我脸上
when you purposely flew that plane into my face.
你是个禽兽 杰
You're a monster, Jay.
你说谁是禽兽
Who are you calling a monster?
他刚说了 是杰
Um, he just said -- Jay.
太不值了
This isn't worth it!
我就不该跟别人一起做任何事
Why do I do anything with people?
我很确定你没有脑震荡
I'm pretty sure you don't have a concussion,
但为了以防万一 我在这陪你
but I'm gonna stay here just in case,
不让你睡着
so you don't fall asleep.
歌洛莉亚 你去叫邓太太过来好吗
Gloria, should you go get Mrs. D?
当然 我看看能不能找到她
Oh, yeah, sure. I'll see if I can find her.
克莱尔
Claire?
看到小卡了吗
Seen Cam?
也祝您感恩节快乐
And a Happy Thanksgiving to you.
脾气真大 你听起来跟我爸一样
Oh, that's a lot of attitude. You sound like my dad.
是咱爸
Our dad!
你回来了 我刚收到朗吉尼斯的短信
There you are. So, I just, uh, got a text message from Longinus.
他说你把墨镜落在感朋节派对上了
Said you left your sunglasses at his Friendsgiving party --
那个你判定我们没时间去的派对
the one you decreed we didn't have enough time to go to.
米奇尔 你欠我一个道歉
Mitchell, you owe me an apology.
我欠你一个道歉
I owe you an apology?
尽管我没带礼物去朗吉尼斯的派对
I may not have brought a gift to Longinus' party,
但我可收到一份大礼
but I sure left with one.
就像他连别人哭都没见过似的
It's like he's never seen someone cry before.
想想难过的事
Just think of something sad.
例如宠物死掉
Like when a pet died,
或是勒迈克去做金球奖填空座的
or when L'Michael was a seat filler at the Golden Globes
结果身边居然是妮可·基德曼
and got to sit next to Nicole Kidman.
他丫凭什么
Why him?!
托勒密 这件事你必须看开
Ptolemy, you must get over that.
我们都围着小卡转的唯一原因是
Look, the only reason we all rallied around Cam was,
你们上次分手时
last time y'all broke up,
他崩溃了 而你似乎没事
he was shattered and you seemed fine.
什么上次分手
What last time?
貌似好多年前
Apparently, years ago,
小卡假装他和我分手了
Cam invented a breakup that never really happened,
就为了估摸一下万一我们真的分手了
just so he could gauge how much support he could count on
会有多少人关心他
in the event of the real thing.
太"正常"了
Normal.
都怪我太过爱他
It's my fault for loving him too much!
不不不不
No! No! No! No!
-你能找到更好的 -别这么对自己
- You can do so much better. - Don't do this to yourself.
-亲爱的 -就是说
- Honey. - Yes.
你让所有人都不站在我这边
You turned everyone against me!
因为情侣分手后 朋友们会选择一边
Because in a breakup, friends choose a side,
而我比你更脆弱 我会更需要他们
and I'm-I'm more fragile, and I would need them more.
我只是为了紧急情况未雨绸缪
I was just preparing for an emergency.
你买地震急救包的时候我对你生气了吗
I didn't yell at you when you bought that, uh, earthquake kit.
你告诉他们我会几天不见人
You told them I disappear for days at a time.
你之所以知道这些
Which you wouldn't know about
都是因为背着我自己去了派对
had you not gone to the party behind my back.
我们之间的信任哪去了 米奇尔
Where's the trust, Mitchell?
这地方看起来很适合躲避狗血剧
Looks like a good place to hide from the drama.
爸 我现在很生你老婆的气
Dad, I am so mad at your wife right now.
-我得建一整幢客房 -不不不
- I need a guest house. - No, no, no.
她完全是在利用我的坐立不安
She-She has completely taken advantage of my restlessness
基本上让我变成了她的管家
and basically turned me into her housekeeper.
怎么做的 故意做不好某件事
How? By doing something the wrong way,
知道你肯定会插手做到完美吗
knowing you'll jump in and do it the right way?
我是怎么回事 为什么总刷不干净杯子
What's wrong with me? Why can't I get these clean?
门都没有
Not gonna happen.
我也有责任
I am partly to blame.
我这个人就是闲不下来
I'm not good at doing nothing.
他们指纹是怎么沾进杯子内侧的啊
How did they get fingerprints on the inside of the glass?
真是要命了
It's crazy.
我刚把公司交接给你的时候也有这情况
You know, I had a similar experience when I turned the company over to you.
我怀念的不是公司的各种事务
It wasn't the activity that I missed.
我怀念的是当老板的感觉
I missed being the boss.
是的 我有同感
Oh! Yeah. I hear you there.
发号施令 令员工闻风丧胆
Giving orders, people scared of you.
我喜爱白日喝酒 但更喜爱在权力中沉醉
I like day drinking, but nothing beats being drunk with power.
是啊
Yeah.
猜猜我在公司说过多少个难笑笑话
Do you know how many unfunny jokes I told at the office?
-零个 -没错
- None? - Exactly.
叩叩叩[常见笑话开头] "哈哈哈哈哈哈
Knock knock. "Ha ha ha ha!
太好笑啦 老板 哈哈哈哈哈
Good one, boss! Ha ha ha ha!
您是怎么一直那么有哏的啊"
How do you keep coming up with them?"
没骨气的马屁精
Spineless bootlickers.
天啊 我好想念他们
God, I miss them.
你是怎么熬过来的
How did you get over it?
我并没有等别人再来给我领导大位
I didn't wait around for someone to put me in charge again.
而是自己创造机会
I made my own opportunity.
老爸 卖狗床吗
Dad, dog beds?
比杆子强多了
Better than poles.
是的 我也是有听到事情的
Oh, yeah. I hear things.
好啦
Alright.
双胞胎现在由迪兰在照顾
Dylan is on twin duty,
所以我得确保你没有睡着
so I'm gonna make sure you don't fall asleep.
我过去十年根本如睡死了一般
I've been asleep for the last 10 years.
想象一下发现自己碰到的撞机事件并不是意外
Imagine finding out the plane crash you were in was no accident.
你不孤单
Well, you're not alone.
杰也对我做过这类的事情
Jay did something very similar to me
我跟米奇尔刚在一起时也发生过
when Mitchell and I first got together.
他"意外"开车碰撞到我
He "accidentally" bumped me with his car --
真的车 可不是遥控玩具
a real car, not a -- not a toy.
我挺伤痕累累的
I was pretty bruised up.
我... 我一开始还以为
I just -- I just assumed it was because
他是见不得儿子找了个男人
he didn't want his son with a boyfriend,
但其实是他觉得米奇尔可以找到更好的
but he thought Mitchell could do better.
我当时真是有点震惊
It was a-a bit of a shock.
但是当我后来也成为人父后
But then, once I became a father,
我意识到了自己也有多护犊子
I realized how protective you can be over your kid.
莉莉的足球队上有个小男孩总闹她
There was a little boy on Lily's soccer team always teasing her,
所以在赛季末派对时
so at the end-of-the-season party,
我貌似意外地把他的脸
I may have nudged him face-first
摁进了一个新做好的炸蛋糕
into a freshly fried funnel cake.
我不得不承认 的确是有可能
It is possible that I have more in common
我跟杰这样的爸爸 有很多共同之处
with dads like Jay than I would like to admit.
邓先生 抱歉我吃掉了最后一个华夫饼
Sorry I ate the last waffle, Mr. D.
我最近特别饿
I've been so hungry lately.
不知道是不是代表我跟海莉又怀了
I wonder if that means we're pregnant again.
哎呀 糟糕
Oh, shoot!
糟糕
Shoot!
糟糕 糟糕 糟糕
Shoot, shoot, shoot.
恭喜你 艾丽克斯
Congratulations, Alex.
一群快饿死的兔子也不愿意吃这胡萝卜
A warren of starving rabbits wouldn't eat these carrots.
我开始考虑我们是不是只应该保持肉体关系了
I'm starting to wonder if our relationship should just be sexual.
好了 尼尔 说实话...
Okay, Neil, honestly --
两位爱侣 这些事之后再说
Hey, hey, hey, you lovebirds! Time for that later.
我们还有大餐要准备呢
We got a meal to finish.
谁快打给联邦应急管理局 这蛋白酥就是场灾难
Can somebody call FEMA? This meringue is a disaster.
我只是照你说的做了
I just did what you told me.
是吗 我有叫你没打发蛋白吗
Oh, really? I told you to underbeat the egg whites?
我真的觉得...
I really think --
我觉得你就是这样
I think. You do.
尼尔 你帮完艾丽克斯了吗
Oh, Neil. Are you done with Alex?
我磨杏仁这一步碰到了一点问题
'Cause I'm having trouble slivering these almonds.
与我合体
Be one with me.
杰
Hey, Jay, um...
我今天好像反应过度了
I think I overreacted earlier.
我想跟你道歉
I want to apologize.
算了啦
Forget it.
我如果说实话 或许某种程度上
If I'm being honest, maybe on some level...
我真是故意用飞机去撞你的
I really did want to hit you with that plane.
抱歉啊 菲尔
I'm sorry, Phil.
谢谢
Thank you.
或许我... 现在也能理解
Maybe I, uh, understand better
爸爸会想要保护女儿的心情
why a father might want to protect a daughter.
或是保护儿子
Or a son.
在我认可小卡前 我也狠狠撞过他一次
I banged Cam up pretty good before I gave him the nod.
他一直都没发现是故意的
He never figured it out.
我也有这种冲动 我承认我也有罪
I get the impulse. I'm -- I'm guilty of it myself.
但排解愤怒应该有比伤害他人
But there's got to be a better way of handling anger
更好的办法吧
than hurting someone, right?
太恶心了吧
Disgusting!
如果这是史上第一次感恩节
If this was the first Thanksgiving,
那你这肉汁就是这个国家
your gravy would be the worst thing
对原住民做过最坏的事情了吧
this country has done to Native Americans!
兄弟
Hey, buddy.
怎么了
Yeah?
绝非有意的意外啊
What a senseless accident.
搞屁啊
What the hell?!
又不是什么大不了的事情
It's not the end of the world.
厨师不需要嗅觉啦
Chefs don't need to smell things.
你们这帮人神经病啊 我要走了
You people are crazy. I'm getting out of here.
真是个绝佳的好主意啊
What a splendid idea.
享受这被毁蛋奶酥吧
Enjoy the souffle.
你最好了
You're the best.
怎么回事 刚才是大厨走的声音吗
Whoa. What's going on? Did I just hear the chef leave?
没救了 我连这是什么都看不出来
It's hopeless. I can't even tell what this was.
我问问有有没有餐厅有位子吧
Well, I'll see if there's a restaurant that can take us.
我们回家吧
I'm just going home.
不不不不不 不行
No. No, no, no, no! Whoa, whoa, whoa! No!
谁都不准走
No one is going anywhere.
听我说 其实我们还能挽救这个感恩节
Listen, you know what? We can salvage this Thanksgiving.
菲尔 去开始搞沙拉
Phil, you get the salad started.
卢克 任何没完全毁掉的东西
Luke, anything you don't need
都留着抢救
dental records to identify, save.
艾丽克斯 那男的就是个傻逼 找个好点的
Alex, that guy was an idiot. Pick better boyfriends.
对不起了 妈 我很想帮你搞定的
I'm sorry, Mom. I so wanted to do this for you.
亲爱的 没事
Oh, honey, no.
你给了我最棒的礼物
You gave me the best gift ever.
我又可以指挥使唤大家了
I'm bossing people around again!
卢克 切点胡萝卜
Luke, chop some carrots.
听我说 我那时只是...
Look, I guess I just --
觉得如果哪天你离开我了 我一定活不下去
I didn't think I would be able to survive if you ever left me.
我此刻还是这么认为
And I still don't.
谢谢
Thank you.
那派对也没那么好玩啦
And the party wasn't that fun.
缺了点什么
Something was missing.
我就喜欢你说事不说明白的姿态
Oh, I love when you say things without really saying them.
你是指我 对吧
You meant me, right?
《无脸的男人》
Man without a face.
《木乃伊》
The mummy.
《昏迷》
Coma.
《我 机器人》
I-robot?
《冰雪奇缘》
Frozen?
《哭泣的游戏》
The crying game.
你们是不是傻啊
What is wrong with you people?
如果你们想看哭泣
If you want to see crying,
那他应该跟着我进厨房
he should come and see me in the kitchen
看看有多少脏碗盘要洗
with all these dirty dishes.
行行行 我帮忙洗盘子跟银制餐具
Fine. I'll do plates and I'll do silverware.
但拒绝需要先泡过再洗的东西
But nothing that requires soaking.
你们可真可爱
You guys are so cute.
乔治可爱
Well... George is.
但茵素需要有点个性
Poppy is going to need a personality.
抱歉了兄弟
Oh! Sorry dude.
绝对是意外
Total accident.
他会是一个好爸爸
He's gonna be a good dad.